<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!--  Titles  -->
    <string name="title_rugby">Rugby</string>
    <string name="title_cricket">Cricket</string>
    <string name="title_basketball">Basketball</string>
    <string name="title_hockey">Hockey</string>
    <string name="title_volleyball">Volleyball</string>
    <string name="title_esports">Esports</string>
    <string name="title_kabbadi">Kabaddi</string>
    <string name="title_baseball">Baseball</string>
    <string name="title_mma">MMA</string>
    <string name="title_soccer">Soccer</string>
    <string name="title_handball">Handball</string>
    <string name="title_tennis">Tennis</string>

    <!--  About  -->
    <string name="about_rugby">
        Rugby union, widely known simply as rugby, is a full contact team sport that originated in
        England in the first half of the 19th century. One of the two codes of rugby football, it is
        based on running with the ball in hand. In its most common form, a game is played between two
        teams of 15 players using an oval-shaped ball on a rectangular field called a pitch. The field
        has H-shaped goalposts at both ends.
        Rugby union is a popular sport around the world, played by male and female players of all ages.
        Rules do not differ between the sexes. In 2014, there were more than 6 million people playing
        worldwide, of whom 2.36 million were registered players. World Rugby, previously called the
        International Rugby Football Board (IRFB) and the International Rugby Board (IRB), has been
        the governing body for rugby union since 1886, and currently has 101 countries as full members
        and 18 associate members.
    </string>

    <string name="about_cricket">
        Cricket is a bat-and-ball game played between two teams of eleven players on a field at the
        centre of which is a 20-metre (22-yard) pitch with a wicket at each end, each comprising two
        bails balanced on three stumps. The batting side scores runs by striking the ball bowled at
        the wicket with the bat, while the bowling and fielding side tries to prevent this and dismiss
        each player (so they are "out"). Means of dismissal include being bowled, when the ball hits
        the stumps and dislodges the bails, and by the fielding side catching the ball after it is
        hit by the bat, but before it hits the ground. When ten players have been dismissed, the
        innings ends and the teams swap roles. The game is adjudicated by two umpires, aided by a
        third umpire and match referee in international matches. They communicate with two off-field
        scorers who record the matches statistical information.
    </string>

    <string name="about_basketball">
        Basketball is a team sport in which two teams, most commonly of five players each, opposing
        one another on a rectangular court, compete with the primary objective of shooting a basketball
        (approximately 9.4 inches (24 cm) in diameter) through the defenders hoop (a basket 18 inches
        (46 cm) in diameter mounted 10 feet (3.048 m) high to a backboard at each end of the court)
        while preventing the opposing team from shooting through their own hoop. A field goal is worth
        two points, unless made from behind the three-point line, when it is worth three. After a foul,
        timed play stops and the player fouled or designated to shoot a technical foul is given one
        or more one-point free throws. The team with the most points at the end of the game wins,
        but if regulation play expires with the score tied, an additional period of play (overtime)
        is mandated.
        Players advance the ball by bouncing it while walking or running (dribbling) or by passing
        it to a teammate, both of which require considerable skill. On offense, players may use a
        variety of shots—the lay-up, the jump shot, or a dunk; on defense, they may steal the ball
        from a dribbler, intercept passes, or block shots; either offense or defense may collect a
        rebound, that is, a missed shot that bounces from rim or backboard. It is a violation to lift
        or drag ones pivot foot without dribbling the ball, to carry it, or to hold the ball with
        both hands then resume dribbling.
    </string>

    <string name="about_hockey">
        Hockey is a sport in which two teams play against each other by trying to manoeuvre a ball
        or a puck into the opponents goal using a hockey stick. There are many types of hockey such
        as bandy, field hockey, ice hockey and rink hockey.
        In most of the world, the term hockey by itself refers to field hockey, while in Canada, the
        United States, Russia and most of Eastern and Northern Europe, the term usually refers to ice
        hockey.
    </string>

    <string name="about_volleyball">
        Volleyball is a team sport in which two teams of six players are separated by a net. Each
        team tries to score points by grounding a ball on the other teams court under organized
        rules. It has been a part of the official program of the Summer Olympic Games since Tokyo
        1964.
        The complete set of rules are extensive, but play essentially proceeds as follows: a
        player on one of the teams begins a rally by serving the ball (tossing or releasing it
        and then hitting it with a hand or arm), from behind the back boundary line of the court,
        over the net, and into the receiving teams court. The receiving team must not let the
        ball be grounded within their court. The team may touch the ball up to 3 times, but individual
        players may not touch the ball twice consecutively. Typically, the first two touches are
        used to set up for an attack, an attempt to direct the ball back over the net in such a way
        that the serving team is unable to prevent it from being grounded in their court.
    </string>

    <string name="about_esports">
        Esports (also known as electronic sports, e-sports, or eSports) is a form of sport competition
        using video games. Esports often takes the form of organized, multiplayer video game
        competitions, particularly between professional players, individually or as teams. Although
        organized competitions have long been a part of video game culture, these were largely between
        amateurs until the late 2000s, when participation by professional gamers and spectatorship in
        these events through live streaming saw a large surge in popularity. By the 2010s,
        esports was a significant factor in the video game industry, with many game developers actively
        designing and providing funding for tournaments and other events.
        The most common video game genres associated with esports are multiplayer online battle arena
        (MOBA), first-person shooter (FPS), fighting, card games, battle royales, and real-time strategy
        (RTS). Popular esport franchises include League of Legends, Dota, Counter-Strike, Overwatch,
        Super Smash Bros., and StarCraft, among many others. Tournaments such as the League of Legends
        World Championship, Dota 2s International, the fighting game-specific Evolution Championship
        Series (EVO) and Intel Extreme Masters are among the most popular in esports. Many other
        competitions use a series of league play with sponsored teams, such as the Overwatch League.
        Although the legitimacy of esports as a true sporting competition remains in question, they
        have been featured alongside traditional sports in some multinational events in Asia, with
        the International Olympic Committee also having discussed their inclusion into future Olympic
        events.
    </string>

    <string name="about_kabbadi">
        Kabaddi is a contact team sport, native to the Indian subcontinent, played between two
        teams of seven players each. The objective of the game is for a single player on offense,
        referred to as a "raider", to run into the opposing teams half of a court, tag out as many
        of their defenders as possible, and return to their own half of the court, all without being
        tackled by the defenders, and in a single breath. Points are scored tagged by the raider,
        while the opposing team earns a point for stopping the raider. Players are taken out of the
        game if they are tagged or tackled, but are brought back in for each point scored by their
        team from a tag or tackle.
        It is popular in South Asia and other surrounding Asian countries. Although accounts of
        kabaddi appear in the histories of ancient India, the game was popularised as a competitive
        sport in the 20th century. It is the national sport of Bangladesh. It is the state game
        of the Indian states of Andhra Pradesh, Bihar, Haryana, Karnataka, Kerala, Maharashtra, Odisha,
        Punjab, Tamil Nadu, Telangana, and Uttar Pradesh.
        There are two major disciplines of kabaddi: so-called Punjabi kabaddi, also referred to as
        circle style, comprises traditional forms of the sport that are played on a circular field
        outdoors, while the standard style, played on a rectangular court indoors, is the discipline
        played in major professional leagues and international competitions such as the Asian Games.
    </string>

    <string name="about_baseball">
        Baseball is a bat-and-ball game played between two opposing teams who take turns batting and
        fielding. The game proceeds when a player on the fielding team, called the pitcher, throws a
        ball which a player on the batting team tries to hit with a bat. The objective of the offensive
        team (batting team) is to hit the ball into the field of play, allowing its players to run the
        bases, having them advance counter-clockwise around four bases to score what are called "runs".
        The objective of the defensive team (fielding team) is to prevent batters from becoming runners,
        and to prevent runners advance around the bases. A run is scored when a runner legally
        advances around the bases in order and touches home plate (the place where the player started
        as a batter). The team that scores the most runs by the end of the game is the winner.
        The first objective of the batting team is to have a player reach first base safely. A player
        on the batting team who reaches first base without being called "out" can attempt to advance
        to subsequent bases as a runner, either immediately or during teammates turns batting. The
        fielding team tries to prevent runs by getting batters or runners "out", which forces them
        out of the field of play. Both the pitcher and fielders have methods of getting the batting
        teams players out. The opposing teams switch back and forth between batting and fielding;
        the batting teams turn to bat is over once the fielding team records three outs. One turn
        batting for each team constitutes an inning. A game is usually composed of nine innings, and
        the team with the greater number of runs at the end of the game wins. If scores are tied at
        the end of nine innings, extra innings are usually played. Baseball has no game clock, although
        most games end in the ninth inning.
    </string>

    <string name="about_mma">
        Mixed martial arts (MMA), sometimes referred to as cage fighting, is a full-contact combat sport
        based on striking, grappling and ground fighting, made up from various combat sports and martial
        arts from around the world, The first documented use of the term mixed martial arts was in a
        review of UFC 1 by television critic Howard Rosenberg in 1993. The term gained popularity
        when newfullcontact.com, then one of the largest websites covering the sport, hosted and
        republished the article. The question of who actually coined the term is subject to debate.
        During the early 20th century, various interstylistic contests took place throughout Japan
        and in the countries of the Four Asian Tigers. In Brazil, there was the sport of Vale Tudo,
        in which fighters from various styles fought with little to no rules. The Gracie family was
        known to promote Vale Tudo matches as a way to promote their own Brazilian jiu-jitsu style.
        An early high-profile mixed martial arts bout was fought in 1951, between the judoka Masahiko
        Kimura and Brazilian jiu-jitsu founder Hélio Gracie in Brazil. In the West, the concept of
        combining elements of multiple martial arts was popularized by Bruce Lees Jeet Kune Do during
        the late 1960s to early 1970s. A precursor to modern MMA was the 1976 Muhammad Ali vs. Antonio
        Inoki bout, fought between boxer Muhammad Ali and wrestler Antonio Inoki in Japan, where it
        later inspired the foundation of Pancrase in 1993 and Pride Fighting Championships in 1997.
    </string>

    <string name="about_soccer">
        Association football, more commonly known as football or soccer, is a team sport played
        with a spherical ball between two teams of 11 players. It is played by approximately 250
        million players in over 200 countries and dependencies, making it the worlds most popular
        sport. The game is played on a rectangular field called a pitch with a goal at each end.
        The object of the game is to score by moving the ball beyond the goal line into the opposing
        goal.
        Football is played in accordance with a set of rules known as the Laws of the Game. The ball
        is 68–70 cm (27–28 in) in circumference and known as the football. The two teams each compete
        to get the ball into the other teams goal (between the posts and under the bar), thereby
        scoring a goal. The team that has scored more goals at the end of the game is the winner;
        if both teams have scored an equal number of goals then the game is a draw. Each team is led
        by a captain who has only one official responsibility as mandated by the Laws of the Game:
        to represent their team in the coin toss prior to kick-off or penalty kicks.
        Players are not allowed to touch the ball with hands or arms while it is in play, except for
        the goalkeepers within the penalty area. Other players mainly use their feet to strike or pass
        the ball, but may also use any other part of their body except the hands and the arms. The
        team that scores most goals by the end of the match wins. If the score is level at the end of
        the game, either a draw is declared or the game goes into extra time or a penalty shootout
        depending on the format of the competition.
    </string>

    <string name="about_handball">
        Handball (also known as team handball, European handball or Olympic handball) is a team
        sport in which two teams of seven players each (six outcourt players and a goalkeeper) pass
        a ball using their hands with the aim of throwing it into the goal of the other team. A
        standard match consists of two periods of 30 minutes, and the team that scores more goals wins.
        Modern handball is played on a court of 40 by 20 metres (131 by 66 ft), with a goal in the
        middle of each end. The goals are surrounded by a 6-meter (20 ft) zone where only the defending
        goalkeeper is allowed; goals must be scored by throwing the ball from outside the zone or while
        "diving" into it. The sport is usually played indoors, but outdoor variants exist in the forms
        of field handball, Czech handball (which were more common in the past) and beach handball.
        The game is fast and high-scoring: professional teams now typically score between 20 and 35
        goals each, though lower scores were not uncommon until a few decades ago. Some players may
        score hat tricks. Body contact is permitted: the defenders trying to stop the attackers from
        approaching the goal. No protective equipment is mandated, but players may wear soft protective
        bands, pads and mouth guards.
    </string>

    <string name="about_tennis">
        Tennis is a racket sport that can be played individually against a single opponent (singles)
        or between two teams of two players each (doubles). Each player uses a tennis racket that is
        strung with cord to strike a hollow rubber ball covered with felt over or around a net and
        into the opponents court. The object of the game is to maneuver the ball in such a way that
        the opponent is not able to play a valid return. The player who is unable to return the ball
        will not gain a point, while the opposite player will.
        Tennis is an Olympic sport and is played at all levels of society and at all ages. The sport
        can be played by anyone who can hold a racket, including wheelchair users. The modern game of
        tennis originated in Birmingham, England, in the late 19th century as lawn tennis. It had
        close connections both to various field (lawn) games such as croquet and bowls as well as to
        the older racket sport today called real tennis. During most of the 19th century, in fact,
        the term tennis referred to real tennis, not lawn tennis.
        The rules of modern tennis have changed little since the 1890s. Two exceptions are that from
        1908 to 1961 the server had to keep one foot on the ground at all times, and the adoption of
        the tiebreak in the 1970s. A recent addition to professional tennis has been the adoption of
        electronic review technology coupled with a point-challenge system, which allows a player to
        contest the line call of a point, a system known as Hawk-Eye.
    </string>


</resources>